When we're predicting today's volatility,
在预测今天的波动率时
we may think that data from the past month are important,
我们可能认为上个月的数据很重要
but what happened yesterday is even more important than what happened last week.
但是昨天的数据比上个星期的数据更重要
This introduces another possibility for how to estimate volatility.
这就引出了估算波动率的另一种方式
What we can do to increase the influence of the more recent past is weight,
为了提高最近过去数据的影响
log return observations from different days, differently.
我们可以对不同日期的对数收益率观察值设置不同的权重
One common method is to weigh the observation from yesterday, the highest,
一种常见方法是对昨天的观察值设置最高的权重
the one from the day before a little less,
对前天的值设置的权重稍微低些
the day before that a little less,
对再前一天的值设置的权重更低些
and so on into the past.
以此类推
In fact, the weights decrease by the same percent with
实际上 权重每一步下降的百分比一样
every step which means they decrease exponentially.
也就是按指数下降
As a result, this is called an exponentially weighted moving average.
所以称为指数加权移动平均
Let's see how to calculate it.
下面看看如何计算
Let's start with the formula for historical volatility.
先看看历史波动率的公式
Let's imagine we're estimating today's volatility using a window of n past days.
假设我们使用 n 天前的窗口估算今天的波动率
We'll add the subscript t to indicate that we are calculating today's volatility.
添加一个下标 t 表示我们计算的是今天的波动率
Let's square both sides.
对两边求平方
Remember, Sigma squared is the variance but we can always take
Σ^2 表示方差
its square root to get the standard deviation i.e. the volatility.
但是我们可以求平方根 得出标准差 即波动率
Now, let's make some simplifications.
下面简化下这个方程
Let's assume that the mean log return is zero.
假设对数收益率期望为零
This is okay to do because when you have
这么简化没啥问题
log returns calculated over a short time interval,
因为如果计算很短时间内的对数收益率
like daily log returns,
例如每日对数收益率
their mean is generally small compared to their standard deviation.
均值与标准差相比通常很小
Now, let's change n minus one to n,
下面将 n-1 变成 n
this simplification won't influence the result much when n is large,
当 n 很大时 这样简化对结果影响不大
and allows us to write the estimate of the variance this way.
使方差的估算公式变成了这样
As you can see, this is just an average of
可以看出 这是平方对数收益率的平均值
the squared log returns in which each squared log return is weighted equally.
其中每个平方对数收益率的权重相同
Let's change the arithmetic average to a weighted average and make
我们将算术平均值变成加权平均值
the weights decrease with each step into the past like we discussed earlier.
然后像之前讨论的那样使权重在往过去的每一步都变小
We're going to introduce a new parameter and lets call it Lambda.
我们将引入一个新的参数 称为 λ
Lambda is a number between zero and one,
λ 是一个介于 0 到 1 之间的数字
and it represents the factor by which the weights in
表示当我们往过去看时
the weighted average decrease as we go back in time.
加权平均中的权重下降因子
So, let's construct the sum.
我们来看看求和公式
The first term will be yesterday's log return squared,
第一项是昨天的对数收益率平方
multiplied by Lambda to the zeroth power which equals one.
乘以 λ 的 0 次幂 等于 1
The next term will be Lambda times the log return of the day before squared.
下一项为 λ 乘以前一天的对数收益率平方
And the next term will have another factor of Lambda.
再下一项将有另一个 λ 因子
This keeps going until we have a term for every log return in our window.
继续下去 直到窗口中的每个对数收益率都对应一项
Now, to make it a weighted average,
要变成加权平均值
we just have to divide by the sum of the weights, and that's it.
只需除以权重之和
That's the formula for an exponentially weighted,
这就是对数收益率方差的
moving average estimate of the variance of the log returns.
指数加权移动平均估算值公式
So to get the volatility,
要计算波动率
we would just take the square root of that estimate.
我们只需计算该估算值的平方根